xpango.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Xpango.com

  * Register
  * Sign in

3,867,959 Xpangoer's and counting...

  * mobile phones
    *     * 

#### Free iPhone

Free iPhone 7, iPhone 7 Plus, iPhone 6s, SE & more...

    * 

#### Free Samsung

Free Samsung Galaxy S5, Galaxy Alpha & more...

    * 

#### Free Nokia

Free Nokia Lumia 920, Lumia 820 and more...

    * 

#### Free HTC

Free HTC One, HTC 8X, HTC 8S and more...

    * 

#### Free Blackberry

Free Blackberry Z10, Bold 9900 and more...

    * **View all Free Mobile Phones »**
  * games consoles
    *     * 

#### Free Xbox One

Free Xbox One, Xbox 360, games and more

    * 

#### Free Sony PS4

Free Sony PS4, PS3, PS Vita, Games and more...

    * 

#### Free Nintendo Wii U

Free Nintendo Wii U, Nintendo 3DS, Games and more...

    * **View all Free Gaming Consoles »**
  * mp3 players
    *     * 

#### Free Apple iPod

Free iPod Touch, iPod Nano and more...

    * 

#### Free Beats Headphones

Free Beats Solo Headphones & more...

    * 

#### Free Sony Walkman

Free Sony Walkman F Series, E Series and more...

    * **View all Free MP3 Players »**
  * tablet/mac
    *     * 

#### Free Apple iPad

Free Apple iPad Pro, iPad Air 2, iPad Mini 4 and more...

    * 

#### Free Samsung Galaxy Tab

Free Samsung Galaxy Tab, Galaxy Tab 2 & more...

    * 

#### Free Kindle

Free Kindle, Kindle Fire and more...

    * 

#### Free Google Nexus

Free Google Nexus 7, Nexus 10 and more...

    * 

#### Free Microsoft Surface

Free Microsoft Surface, plus keyboard and more...

    * **View all Free Tablet/Mac »**
  * gift cards
    *     * 

#### Free iTunes Gift Cards

Free Apple iTunes Gift Cards, App Store Cards and more...

    * 

#### Free Amazon Gift Cards

Free Amazon Gift Cards, MP3 Gift Cards and more...

    * **View all Free Gift Cards »**

Xpango are committed to protecting your privacy. We hope the following privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") will help you understand how we collect and protect the personal information you provide to us when registering with the Xpango.com web site (the "Site") and by Xpango Ltd. 

We are committed to making your use of the Site easy and enjoyable as possible. Please take a moment to read the following Privacy Policy to determine how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our offers. 

By using the Site, or providing the information requested by the Site, or by continuing to use the Site after having an opportunity to review this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy and our use of the information we collect. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. 

Xpango Ltd reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without giving you prior notice. Your use of the Site following any such modification constitutes your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy as modified. The last date this Privacy Policy was revised or modified is set forth below ("Effective Date"). 

I. What personally identifiable information does Xpango.com collect from me and how does Xpango.com use my information? 

To create an account, we collect your name, email address, and a shipping address. We also collect a password that you create, which you may change in the 'My Account' page of our site. We will initially use this information to set up your account, to send you a registration confirmation email and to log your shipping information so that we know where to send your order. 

Referral emails that you initiate from the "Refer Friends" page of your Xpango.com account will be sent out by Xpango.com on your behalf and will either display your email address or that of "support@xpango.com" in the email "From" field. Referral email addresses are only used to deliver user-initiated communications. Xpango.com will not collect and use these referral email addresses for any other purpose or manner. 

Although Xpango.com may have independently received similar information from your use of the Site, Xpango.com does not have access to any additional information that you provide on a third party hosted site (i.e. if you complete an offer such as Blockbuster.com, Xpango do not have access to the information you submit to Blockbuster). 

All information provided to our third party business partners is subject to the posted privacy policies of our third party business partners. 

When you place an order, your shipping information is sent to a vendor who will fulfill and ship your product(s). Our suppliers will also safeguard your personal information and are contractually prohibited from disclosing your personal information to other parties for any reason. They will not have access to any referral information you provide. 

II. Completing 3rd Party Offers to gain Credits with Xpango.com 

Our goal is to deliver offers to customers who we believe will find them of value. Offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information. When you click on an offer, you will be redirected to that advertiser's site. An instruction box will appear explaining to which offer you are being redirected. Although the site may still display a Xpango.com address on the landing page, you are in fact on a third party offer provider's website, and any information you submit will be transmitted to this third party. 

As a member of the Site, we will be sending transactional emails for various reasons as you continue to use our site. For example, a welcome email will be sent thanking you for joining, or an email telling you an order has shipped, etc. These emails are required for logistical purposes and users cannot opt-out of these types of emails. 

If you contact Xpango.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Wherever Xpango.com collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that specified page. 

With your consent, Xpango.com may from time to time send commercial e-mails with additional Xpango offers and information about New gifts available from Xpango. Xpango.com is committed to ethical and responsible e-mail practices. Accordingly, Xpango.com strives to make sure that all commercial e-mails sent by Xpango.com are compliant with the Can-Spam Act of 2003. Members may opt-out of receiving promotional mailings by clicking on the opt-out link contained in the body of any commercial e-mail sent by Xpango.com or by unsubscribing from commercial e-mail by logging into your Member account on Xpango.com, clicking on the unsubscribe link and entering the e-mail address that you wish to unsubscribe from further commercial e-mail messages from Xpango.com. 

Please note that we can only allow one account per household. This rule exists to protect our advertising partners, as it serves to engender high quality, unique leads. Potential users who reside in households with multiple people are recommended to share an account. 

Keep in mind that if you take advantage of an offer from a Xpango.com business partner and thus, become their customer, they may independently wish to send offers to you. In the event that you are not interested in receiving future offers from these affiliates, you must contact them directly to fulfill your list removal request. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site. If your personally identifiable information changes, you may update it by making the necessary edits by logging into your account at Xpango.com and clicking on the 'Edit My Details' link. 

To deactivate an account, please contact Customer Service directly with this request. 

II. What are cookies and how does Xpango.com use them? 

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Xpango.com uses cookies to better understand your traffic patterns on the Site as well as keeping your login information securely stored. This information helps us improve the navigation and flow of the web site. Additionally this may allow users who choose to be remembered when they come back to the Site to be automatically logged in. We link cookies to personally identifiable information so that we may track your activities on the Site in order to credit you for completing a third party offer. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you choose to disable the use of cookies, you will run the risk of not receiving proper credit for completing an offer. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers/offer providers) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these types of cookies. 

III. Who is collecting information? 

When you are on a Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Xpango.com, unless it is specifically stated otherwise in this Privacy Policy or in a 3rd party offer that you may be asked to complete as part of utilizing the service. 

Please be aware that Xpango.com partners, advertisers and web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Internet access partners, advertisers, and web sites linked from Xpango.com are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Xpango.com has no liability or responsibility for these independent policies or the use of any personally identifiable information you independently transfer to these companies. 

IV. With whom does Xpango.com share my information? 

As set forth in Section I, Xpango.com may submit your personal information to third party business partners to participate in their offer or survey. Except as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy, Xpango.com will **NOT** disclose any of your personally identifiable information . 

b. Other: Xpango.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Xpango.com's policies or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Xpango.com's rights or property, other Xpango.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Xpango.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. Lastly, Xpango.com may disclose a users e-mail address as part of a suppression file or do-not-e-mail list to its partners and affiliates to make sure that a users unsubscribe requests are forwarded to the appropriate parties to ensure removal of the user from partner and affiliate databases in compliance with law, including without limitation, the Can-Spam Act of 2003. 

c. Acquisitions. As Xpango.com develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that Xpango.com or all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site, would be one of the transferred assets. 

V. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information? 

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Account information for Xpango.com members are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. You may edit your Xpango.com account information by logging into your Member account on Xpango.com, clicking on the 'Edit My Details' link and update your personal information. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Xpango.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your Xpango.com account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library. 

VI. Miscellaneous Provisions. 

a. Disclaimer of Liability. Under no circumstances shall Xpango.com be liable for any damages, including, but not limited to, indirect, special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages, that result from the use of the information or materials posted to or collected as a result of the user's accessing the Site or use of the service provided by Xpango.com, even if Xpango.com has been advised of the possibility of such damages. 

b. Enforcement/Redress. If for some reason you believe that Xpango.com has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please notify Customer Service and they will endeavor to respond to your concerns and, when appropriate, take steps to correct a problem. 

c. Security of the Data Collected. The Site is not a secure web site. Xpango.com cannot and does not ensure or warrant the security of any information collected by use, transmitted over the Internet, or maintained in your user profile. You agree that any data transmission you make or receive through the Site is at your own risk. 

VIII. Additional Information. 

If you have a question that was not addressed in this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by: 

1\. Sending an e-mail request to support@xpango.com; or 

2\. Sending a written letter to: 

Xpango Ltd .  
Customer Services  
Hillview Business Centre  
2 Leybourne Avenue  
Bournemouth  
Dorset   
BH10 6HF  
UK 

*DATE OF LAST MODIFICATION : April 10th, 2011*
